dpchallenge.com 2008-06-16

# DPChallenge - A Digital Photography Contest

_Last Updated: November 25, 2002_

Thank you for visiting DPChallenge.com. We know that you care how information about you is used and shared, and we appreciate your trust. This statement describes our privacy policy. It applies only to DPChallenge.com, so if you visit sites that we link to, be sure to check out their privacy policies. DPChallenge.com reserves the right to revise this policy at any time without notification to you, so please re-read it often in connection with your use of the DPChallenge.com website. 

**What personally identifiable information do we collect and why?**

We collect the personally identifiable information that you submit on the registration form to permit you access to our site, and to enable credit card verification, if applicable. 

Generally, the information DPChallenge.com collects helps us to provide you with the latest product and promotional information we feel you may find useful and to communicate with you regarding media licensed from or to you. For instance, we use your email address to provide you email confirmation of your registration, confirmation of media you have submitted to DPChallenge.com and to notify you of information concerning our site. You can opt-in to receive our newsletter. This information will not be sent to you if you ask us not to include your name on our mailing lists. In many places where personal information is collected, we have a box that you can check indicating that you would like to “opt out,” that is, you do not wish to receive further information of the sort indicated. If you have previously consented to have DPChallenge.com contact you and no longer wish to be contacted, please send us an email at the address below. 

We will not share, rent or sell your personally-identifiable information with any entity, subject to the provisions below. We may share your information with our vendors in connection with system maintenance and other services that these individuals or entities perform for us. In some cases, we may run a joint marketing effort with third parties. You can tell when another company is involved and if you provide personal information in connection with the joint marketing efforts, the info you provide will be shared with that company. Also, in the event that DPChallenge.com is acquired or merged with another company, customer information will be one of the transferred assets. We also release personal information when we believe it is necessary to comply with the law; to enforce or to apply our Terms of Use and other agreements (including our Member Agreement); or to protect the rights, property, or safety of DPChallenge.com, our users or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction. 

**Use of Automatic Information and "Cookies"**

Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser and to provide features like the welcome message and, eventually, your customized DPChallenge.com home page. Further, to help us tailor our site to the needs and interests of our visitors, or for other purposes, we may gather aggregate, non-personally identifiable information via cookies. Examples include the type of Internet browser our visitors are using, the frequency of visits to our site and which pages our visitors viewed. We may share these aggregate statistics with others. The use of cookies is standard on the Internet and many major web sites use them. Cookies stored on your computer do not contain any personally identifiable information, other than your username. 

**Children and DPChallenge.com**

Children may use our site by complying with our parental/guardian consent procedures found in the Terms of Use for DPChallenge.com, but we don’t have any intention of collecting any personally identifiable information from individuals under thirteen years of age. If you are aware that a child has provided us with personally identifiable information, please contact us at the email address listed at the bottom of this Privacy Statement. 

**Updating or Deleting Your Information**

You can change or delete your "optional" information in the My Account section. If you would like to change or hide from the public your "required" information, please contact us via email at [help@DPChallenge.com](mailto:help@dpchallenge.com). 

**Security**

We understand that many consumers are concerned about security on the Internet. The security of the information that you provide to us is also very important to us. To prevent unauthorized disclosure, maintain data accuracy and ensure the correct use of information, we have in place reasonable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure any information we collect online. Our payment systems vendor uses Secure Sockets Layer (SSL), an advanced encryption protocol, to scramble credit card information that you enter so that it cannot be read as it is transmitted across the Internet. SSL is the recognized industry standard worldwide for such sensitive transactions, enhancing safety when you shop with a credit card on the web. It is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer. Be sure to sign off when finished using a shared computer and do not opt to save your username or password on login to DPChallenge.com. In the event that our security system is breached, we will attempt to notify you as soon as possible. 

**Questions?**

If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Statement, the practices of DPChallenge.com, or your dealings on our web site, please email us at [help@DPChallenge.com](mailto:help@dpchallenge.com).   
  
Home \- Challenges \- Community \- League \- Photos \- Cameras \- Lenses \- Learn \- [Prints!](http://www.dpcprints.com/) \- Help \- Terms of Use \- Privacy \- Top ^   
DPChallenge, and website content and design, Copyright © 2001-2008 Challenging Technologies, LLC.   
All digital photo copyrights belong to the photographers and may not be used without permission.   
Proudly hosted by [Sargasso Networks](http://www.sargasso.net/from/dpc). Current Server Time: 06/15/2008 11:44:20 PM EDT.
